There is a video that has been released of three Israeli hostages being held by Hamas
and the video is addressed to Bibi Netanyahu and I want to show you one part of the video
and then explain what she's talking about. I actually can't show you that video because
Instagram keeps taking it down and they took down my original post about this and then
threatened to take my account down so I'm going to give you a quick synopsis of what that video was.
So it was three Israeli hostages talking to the camera to Bibi Netanyahu saying that he was killing
everyone and he needed to stop and saying that they were aware that Hamas offered to release all
of their hostages in exchange for Israel to stop bombing Gaza and Israel said no and she's saying
to free Palestinian citizens, free Palestinian prisoners and to free everyone because they
have the power to do so and they're choosing not to. So she's talking about freeing their prisoners.
She's talking to Bibi Netanyahu and saying free their prisoners. This is the most important
piece of information that you need to understand why all of this started happening in the first
place. All of this I meant the events of October 7th. Everything else has to do with the occupation.
This is a report from the United Nations Human Rights Council back in July of this year.
In this report it says currently there were 5,000 Palestinians in Israeli prisons including
160 children and approximately 1100 of them are being detained without trial or charge. This is
illegal under international law. Under international law these Palestinians being held by Israel are
considered hostages. They have kidnapped and they regularly kidnap Palestinians from their homes,
from their families and imprison them for years without any hint of release or a trial to lead to a
release ever. These are the prisoners this woman is referring to. This is why Hamas took hostages
and I'll explain further. In 2006 Hamas captured an Israeli soldier named Gilad Sherit who was 19 at the
time. In 2011 Israel swapped over a thousand Palestinians being illegally held in Israeli prisons for this one
soldier. Over a thousand Palestinians released in exchange for one soldier. The time of October 7th
when Hamas captured over 200 Israelis they had more than enough to swap out a total exchange to release
all Palestinian prisoners being illegally held by Israel. That was the purpose of taking hostages.
In the last two weeks Israel has kidnapped an additional 5,000 Palestinians. The total of Palestinians
being illegally held in Israeli prisons right now is 10,000. They are illegally holding hostage 10,000
Palestinians. They took 5,000 people in two weeks. They took over 4,000 workers from Gaza and an
additional 1,000 people in occupied West Bank. There is no Hamas in the West Bank. You have to question
why you were so quick to believe that brown people are doing heinous things just for the purpose of being
heinous and being terrible. This is what the media is telling you. That they took these hostages specifically
to be evil, to torture them, to torment them, to kill them. When in actuality as more are being released
all of them are talking about how well they have been treated by the people who captured them. They
have made sure that you have completely ignored the purpose of why all of this happened on October 7th
and it was to release at the time 5,000 Palestinians at the time almost 200 of whom were children being held
hostage for years by Israel. And instead of striking any type of deal or being open to any type of
negotiations to save their own people and have their own people released they just took more of ours
and then they bombed the crap out of the rest of them. If we need to contextualize everything
there's your context.